bollywood-stars.net 2010-12-24

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

This **privacy policy** , hereby, refers for all the privacy practices adopted by **www.bollywood-stars.net** in collecting user information and its dissemination and distribution for a number of customer related services and improvement of the website. We are strictly adhered with policy of non distribution of client information in most of the cases and keeps on applying and modifying privacy policy as according to the change in technology in highly vibrant IT industry.  We have application of privacy policy for Bollywood-stars in the many areas.

There is good number of reasons why a website collects client information? First of all, client information is collected to maintain a proper communication with visitors and users who have subscribed to any of our services. We generally ask for very common user info like name, email address and more during registering this website and any of its services.

Sometimes, Bollywood, also seeks for or gets access to the technical information like IP address, profile information, user data and browser type to performance enhancing tasks like managing the website, tracking its services as used by visitors and to improve website services. User IP address are generally recorded for security and monitoring usages.

Collected e-mail addresses are also used as notifications alerts to a site’s users to send updates, newsletters or introduction to a new service to be launched on a website. More Bollywood star can ask for information, while, organizing a contest online. Bollywood Star can change its privacy policy as according to change occurred in cyber laws or in case of introduction of new technology into cyber space.
